

# **BODINWIWAT PHUNSIRITHAWON**

#### CONTACT

- (a): 208 276 Natakan apartment, Sansen Nok, Huai Khwang, Bangkok 10310
- (C): +669 3168 3755
- (f): Bodinwiwat Phunsirithawon
- (c): sorobe03

#### LANGUAGE

Thia English Native Medinum

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILS**



























#### **TOOLS**

Figma





### **ABOUT ME**

Hello there, My name is Bodinwiwat Phunsirithawon you can call me "Not" I is programmed. I want to learn and gain experience in programming development. in various platforms corporateculture and always seek new knowledge for self-improvement



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Junior Programer, Nippon Sysits Co.,Ltd.

August 2021 - March 2022

#### Xenmed Project

- This is a project about detect medicine
- Frontend development using vue is
- Backend development using express js

#### Xentrack Project

- This is a IoT project about follow people in the building.
- Frontend development using vue js
- Backend development using node-red

#### Demo UTM Project

- This is a IoT project about tracking the flight of drones.
- Frontend development using vue js
- Backend development using node-red

# Junior Frontend Developer, Waylar Tech Co., Ltd

May 2021 - July 2021

Front-end developer experience training

### RF Engineer apprenticeship, Ericsson north chiang mai

December 2020 - March 2021

Check and analyze the results of the phone signal test.



### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor's degree Computer Engineering,

Faculty of Information and Communication Technology University of Phayao

July 2017 - March 2021

### Science-Mathematics, Nanoi School, Nanoi, Nanoi, Nan

July 2011 - March 2017



### REFERENCE

# Assist.porf Sakorn Mekruksavanich, Ph.D.

Project Advisor Computer Engineering Faculty of Information and Communication Technology University of Phayao Tel: +668 1963 0289